snapfiles.com 2010-12-03

# Privacy Policy - SnapFiles.com

### Information Collection and Use

WebAttack, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. WebAttack, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

### Software Store

The Snapfiles Software Store is operated by Cleverbridge, who handle the order processing on behalf of Snapfiles. You can [review the CleverBridge Privacy Policy here](http://www.cleverbridge.com/?scope=contact&id=AKjxhsiZwH&progress=privacy) . 

### Registration

In order to use some parts of this website (e.g. forums or member areas), a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender or personal interests), and unique identifiers, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. Orders/Membership subscriptions We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to use certain features of our bulletin board or other parts of the site that offer customized settings. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Please refer to the privacy policies of the network for details. 

Google Ads  

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html)

Users can opt out of some, but not all, cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative's opt-out website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we WebAttack, Inc. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link http://www.ssl.com 

### Site and Service Update

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email 

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact : 

WebAttack, Inc. - 4044 W. Lake Mary Blv., Unit #104-350, Lake Mary, FL 32746-2012 Email: [email](http://www.snapfiles.com/feedback/)
